

KONTAK

Alamat:

Pulo Gadung, East Jakarta

No Hp:

081363847633

Email:

ulfafitri11@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ulfa-fitri-5a823617b

PENDIDIKAN

UNIVERSITAS ANDALAS (2014-2019)

Sarjana Pertanian (S.P)

Faculty of Agriculture, Agrotechnology GPA 3.24

Thesis

Biologi dan neraca kehidupan wereng batang coklat atau WBC (*Nilaparvata lugens* Stal 1854) (Hemiptera : Delphacidae) pada padi varietas IR42 dan Batang Piaman di Laboratorium.

SKILL

- Microsoft Office
- SPSS
- PicsArt
- Corel DRAW

BAHASA

- Indonesia
- English
- Japan (Basic)

PRESTASI

KemenristekdiktiRI

2017 | Receiver of Peningkatan Prestasi Akademik(PPA) Scholarship.

ULFA FITRI

About Me

I am a graduate from Agriculture of Andalas University. During my time at the college, I was an assistant of lecturer in my faculty. Beside of that, I was also chosen to be participated in KKN facilitated by Dinas Perkebunan Sumatera Barat. I actively participated joining organizations and committees inside and outside the college. Throughout these experiences, I can improve my skills. I am a hard working person, willing to learn new experiences, have a good communication skill and good at working in team or individual, and i am interest in research, leadership

Organizations and Committes

Member (2015 –2016)

Komunitas Receh Indonesia

Responsible doing fundraising and distributing the charity directly to the schools in needs.

Member (2015 - 2016)

Gerakan Mahasiswa Pariaman(GEMPA)

Responsible for organizing SBMPTN trial for free students in Pariaman, and went to scholls to provide students about information to get into colleges

Member of Fundraising and Donation (2016 –2017)

Agricultural Students Community of Andalas University

Responsible in doing fundraising and selling the agricultural products in the faculty, and making the report of it.

Publication and Documentation Staff (2016)

Agriculture In Art and Creative

Responsible in promoting the event in social media and documenting the whole activities.

Experiences

Assistant of Pesticide and Aplication Techniques Laboratory (2018-2019)

Laboratorium Jurusan Perlindungan Tanaman

Giving lecture materials practice for my juniors, input their final tests result online, and made the report of it.

Kelompok Penyelenggara Pemungutan Suara Kota Pariaman(2019) Komisi Pemilihan Umum

Registered the voters and participated in Presidential Election as a KPPS member.

AdminOlshop (2020-2021)

Nike Olshop

Promoted, sold online, and helped the owner in packaging and wrote Shop's monthly income.

Commercial Cookery (2022)

Balai Pelatihan Vokasi dan Produktivitas (BPVP) Padang / BLK

Learned more about basic cooking techniques, cuisines from other countries and basic hospitality lesson for hotel clerk in treating the customers.